NATALIE WOODARD

THE CODING LINGUIST

nwoodard72@gmail.com| (505) 459-1858 www.linkedin.com/in/natalie-woodard github.com/nwoodard1

OBJECTIVE

I am interested in Natural Language Processing as it applies to Artificial Intellegence and research in human language and behaviors. My educational background is in linguistics and I find language processing applications fascinating. I look forward to finding a way to implement that into a software development career.

SKILLS

- Experience in Fullstack Software Development
- Able to successfully manage multiple priorities and meet deadlines.
- Experience annotating audio data within a linguistic setting in a variety of platforms
- Participated in and performed small case studies and research projects in a variety of subjects.
- Learned hands-on skills and tools to conduct surveys and studies in a variety of subjects.
- Eager to learn new skills and get established within my career.
- Ultimate teamworker, I love group projects.

EXPERIENCE

Massage Therapist

- Student Intern at Deep Dive Coding Jan-March 2019 | Albuquerque, NM
- Enlighten Wellness Center, 2018-2019 | Albuquerque, NM
- Por Vida Therapeutics, 2014-2019 | Albuquerque, NM
- Sweet Soul Therapeutic Massage, 2012-2014 | Corrales, NM

Various

Variety of Customer Service and Retail jobs prior to my Massage Therapy Certification

EDUCATION

- Fullstack Web Development Certification, March 2019 ; Deep Dive Coding Bootcamp | Albuquerque, NM
- Bachelor of Arts in Linguistics, May 2018; University of New Mexico | Albuquerque, NM
- Massage Therapist, April 2011; New Mexico School of Natural Therapeutics | LMT 7162 | Albuquerque, NM